epxbody.com 2014-12-17

# EPXBody

At EPX Body, we respect and are committed to protecting your privacy and personal information. Please read the following to learn more about what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, how or when we disclose the information and how we safeguard your personal information. EPX Body’s Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected anytime you interact with EPX Body, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase EPX Body products and services, or when you call our Support Service representatives.

EPX Body may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.

If you have questions or concerns about EPX Body's Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us via email at support@EPXbody.com or by mail at EPX Body Support Services, 1485 West Hillfield Road #202, Layton, Utah 84041.

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**How We Use Personal Information**

We collect your personal information to deliver customer service. It enables us to give you access to our products and services. We collect from you only a minimum of personal information on our websites (such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or credit card information) that is necessary to:

• authenticate and process your order;

• provide you with order support;

• send you communications related to your order; and

• enable you to participate in special offers and other site features.

We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve EPX Body’s services and products.

In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.  If you do not want EPX Body to keep you up-to-date with EPX Body news, software updates, and the latest information on products and services contact support@EPXbody.com and ask to be removed from promotional emails.

**Cookies, Click-Trough’s and Pixel Tags**

Like many websites, "cookies" are used to enable our site's or service provider's systems to recognize your internet browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. This information can include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, date/time stamp, and referring/exit pages. This information, which does not identify individual users, would only be used to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around EPX Body’s sites and to gather miscellaneous demographic information about our visitors as a whole. EPX Body will not collect information to market directly to that person.

If you prefer not to enable cookies, please check the help section of your preferred internet browser for instructions on how you can disable cookies.  Please note that certain features of the EPX Body website may not be available when cookies are disabled.

In some of our email messages we use a “click-through” URL link to content on the EPX Body website. When customers click one of these URL’s, they pass through our web servers before arriving at the destination. EPX Body may track this click-through data to help us measure interest in methods customers prefer to retrieve information and messages. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

EPX Body may use pixel tags, which are tiny graphic images; to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited.

**How We Protect Personal Information**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

We will not share, lease, sell, or otherwise transfer your personal information to any outside parties for their independent use or benefit without first obtaining your permission.  However, we may release your information if we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights and safety.

**Legal Issues**

Please note that EPX Body may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. EPX Body’s internal policies call for the release of required information in the cases of subpoena, court orders and order of local, state and federal government.

**Service Providers and Vendors**

There are also times when EPX Body may need to make certain personal information about you available to companies that perform work for EPX Body on products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with EPX Body’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. ** **

**Third Party Websites**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site.  These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

**Children**

EPX Body does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If a child under 13 submits personal information to EPX Body – and we learn that personal information is the information of a child under 13 – we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. ** **

**How to Modify or Remove Your Information**

If you have opted-in to receive our email newsletter but would no longer like to receive promotional emails from us, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section of our site. Please note that due to email production schedules, you may receive any emails already in production. 

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses, and payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
